原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
翻譯     小酸奶  草草
翻譯     白夜君  蘇葵
校對     小酸奶
時間軸     西·查
后期     吉吉
總監     小酸奶
深入黑暗 第一季 第十二集
凱爾
Kyle.
她真是對你過敏
She is literally allergic to you.
我們快到了  謝伊
We're almost there, Shay.
很快就結束了
It'll be over soon.
抱歉
Sorry.
貞潔
手機
Cell phones.
爸爸  不行
Dad, no.
我也關了我的
I turned mine off too.
交出來
Hand them over.
叛徒
Traitor.
別找麻煩  喬
Hey, don't be difficult, Jo.
凱爾  我的朋友  見到你真高興
Kyle, my friend, it is good to see you.
見到你很高興  牧師
Good to see you, Pastor.
-你還好嗎  -很好  先生
- How you doing, my man? - Oh, very good, sir.
女士們  容我來做迎賓隊
Ladies, allow me to be your welcoming committee.
女兒節快樂
喬  看看你  長這么大了
Jo, look at you, all grown up.
這是第幾次了
How many is this now?
第五次
Number five.
老天爺啊  這是誰
Praise the Lord. And who is this?
這是謝伊
This is Shay.
我的另一個女兒
My other daughter.
很高興你能來  謝伊
Well, it is wonderful to have you, Shay.
我是賽斯牧師
I am Pastor Seth.
認識你很高興
Nice to meet you.
謝伊是第一次來
This is Shay's first time,
她來的途中還有點暈車
and she got a little carsick on the way up.
沒事的
Listen, don't worry,
我們會教你怎么做
we will tell you what to do.
但我有個問題  你祈禱嗎  謝伊
But I do have a question: Do you pray, Shay?
沒怎么祈禱過
I haven't much.
沒事
Well, that's okay.
喬肯定能教你
I'm sure that Jo can help show you how.
是啊  我的確
Yes, I have been known
時不時會采取跪姿
to get on my knees every now and then.
-喬  -為了祈禱
- Jo. - To pray.
你來這里很勇敢  謝伊
You are very brave, Shay, for being here.
這條路可不好走
This is not an easy path to walk in.
很多人一路上磕磕絆絆
Many have stumbled along the way,
但別擔心
but do not worry.
我們不會讓你摔倒的
We will not let you fall.
現在上帝會照顧你了
You're in God's hands now.
謝謝
Thank you.
謝伊
Shay!
快點
Hurry up.
喬  你到了
Jo, you're here!
對  永遠的4號小屋
Yeah, cabin 4 for life.
我爸爸好慌
My dad's freaking out.
他每年都緊張得要死
Literally every year, he's a nervous wreck
直到我們到這里
until we get up here.
喬
Hi, Jo.
我是萊西
Hi, I'm Lacey.
凱利安
KellyAnn.
伙計們  這是謝伊
Guys, this is Shay.
我們是姐妹
We're sisters.
你覺得牧師會講話嗎
Do you think the pastor will do the speech?
可能吧
Probably.
什么講話
What speech?
莉莉絲
Lilith.
喬很喜歡莉莉絲的講話
Jo loves the Lilith speech.
我覺得你可能沒聽懂
I feel like you might be missing the point.
你是不該喜歡那個故事的
You're not supposed to love that story.
拜托告訴我你周日不會戴那個面紗
Please tell me you're not gonna wear that veil on Sunday.
跟裙子一起的
Came with the dress.
不  絕對不要
No! Definitely no.
我為舞會買了兩件裙子
I bought two dresses for the ball.
-為什么  -因為
- Why? - Well,
我爸替我挑裙子  每年
my dad picks out my dress for me, and every year,
他挑的都基本一樣
it's like he picks out the exact same one.
無聊
Boring.
所以今年  我去了商場
So this year I was at the mall
看到了一件完美的裙子
and I saw the perfect one and...
我就沒忍住
I couldn't help myself.
你不會穿的
You'll never wear it.
爸爸的小天使
Daddy's little angel.
你穿什么  謝伊
What are you wearing, Shay?
真美
Oh, that's gorgeous.
是你爸爸選的嗎
Did your dad pick it out?
我試了一堆我喜歡的  但是他挑的
I tried on a bunch that I liked, but yeah.
凱爾說這件最好
Kyle said this one was the best.
你喊你爸凱爾
You call your dad Kyle?
她兩個月前才認識他的
She only met him two months ago.
每年女兒節
Every year on Daughter's Day,
我們都齊聚于此
we gather together here
談論一個年輕姑娘人生中兩段
to talk about the two most important relationships
最重要的關系
in a young girl's life:
她跟天父的關系  阿門
Her relationship with her Heavenly Father, amen...
-阿門  -以及她跟
- Amen. - And her relationship
人間父親的關系  阿門
with her earthly father, amen.
-阿門  -阿門
- Amen. - Amen.
我的女兒  萊西
My own daughter, Lacey,
這是她第十屆舞會
this is her 10th ball.
這是她第十次的貞潔起誓
This is her 10th pledge of purity.
感謝上帝
Woo, thank you, Lord!
父親們都理解我的
You fathers know what I'm talking about, I bet.
我真幸運
Man, am I blessed.
十年前  我開始推動父女們的關系
When I started bringing fathers and daughters together a decade ago,
建立了這間教堂
I built this church,
我做了這些彩窗
and I had these windows made
因為我覺得我必須
because I felt compelled
講述一個不常被講述
to tell a story that is not often told
但如今非常重要的故事
but is vitally important nowadays.
女士們先生們  夏娃并非第一個女人
You see, ladies and gentlemen, Eve was not the first woman.
不是的  你們肯定不知道
No, no, she was not, I bet you didn't know that.
上帝彎下身  拿人間的黏土
When God bent down and made Adam
塑造了亞當時
out of the dust of this earth,
他還拿一樣的黏土做了個女人
he also made a woman out of that same clay,
她叫莉莉絲
and her name was Lilith.
莉莉絲很獨立
Now, Lilith was independent.
很固執
She was strong-willed,
但她也很淫蕩
but she was lustful.
莉莉絲被逮到
Lilith was caught
跟一個天使通奸
fornicating with a member of the heavenly host.
你可以說有個天使吻了她  是的
You might say she was kissed by an angel, yes, she was,
但當我們的主和天父上帝得知后
but when Lord, our God and Father, found out,
他立刻施以了嚴厲的懲罰
his punishment was swift and it was severe.
因為在天上的主  上帝
You see, because our Lord, God above,
把莉莉絲直接送進了地獄
sent Lilith straight to hell.
阿門
Amen.
去地獄
To hell.
然后  天父又為亞當造了個女人
Then, our Father set out to create another woman for Adam,
但這次
but this time,
他是用亞當自己的身體做的
he did so by using a rib from Adam's own body.
是的
Yes, he did.
他說她是個更好的女人
He said she was a better woman,
是的  她是更好
and yes, she was better,
但她也很脆弱
but she was also fragile.
她需要指引
She needed guidance.
我們的主上帝告訴我們
Our Lord God tells us
如果沒有強大的男人提供指引
that without a strong man to offer guidance,
我們的女兒也可能淪落成莉莉絲
our daughters may end up just like Lilith!
她可能會落入地獄
She may end up in hell.
瞧  各位  這是生死大事
See, folks, this is life or death we are talking about here.
生死大事
This is life or death.
這就是我們本周齊聚于此的原因
And that is why we are here this week.
我們祈禱吧
Let us pray.
親愛的天父
Dear Heavenly Father...
我們這周也要拍一張這個
And we're gonna take one of these this week.
其中有你和喬的嗎
Are there any of you and Jo?
她第一年是12歲
Well, her first year she was 12,
她可能翻出來燒了
so she probably found it and burned it.
我每年都滿懷希望地帶她來
I bring her every year hoping, but, uh,
但她就是似乎不怎么喜歡
she just doesn't seem to like it very much.
向我保證
Make me a promise?
這周末
This weekend,
對我非常重要
it's really important to me.
好好試試  謝伊
Give this a shot, Shay.
真正去嘗試
A real shot.
我保證
I promise.
謝伊  來一口嗎
Shay, want a hit?
-好  -怎么了
- Yeah, sure. - What?
等等  怎么回事
Wait, so, what's the deal?
繼姐妹嗎
Half-sisters?
一個爸爸  不是一個媽媽
Uh, same dad, different moms.
但你們是同齡
But you're the same age?
對
Yeah.
凱爾之前不知道我的存在
Kyle didn't even know I existed
直到今年夏天
until, like, this summer,
但他現在想要彌補
but he's trying to do the right thing now,
所以我才來了
so that's why I'm here.
看吧
See?
所以我們今晚不能邀請她
This is why we can't invite her tonight.
她一心想巴結他  她會告密的
She is so far up his ass, she'll just tell him.
告什么密
Tell him what?
穿衣服
Get dressed.
但該睡覺了
But it's bedtime.
我們要去冒險
We're going on a little adventure.
不了  謝謝
Oh, no, thank you.
不  你是個風險
No, you're a liability.
說真的
Seriously,
你的人生也需要點樂子  來吧
you could use a little fun in your life, come on.
我不怎么喜歡冒險
Adventure isn't really my thing, guys,
我還是留下吧
so I'm gonna stay back here.
你真以為我們會留下你
You really think we're just gonna leave you here
讓你跑去告訴你爸嗎
so you can just run and tell Daddy?
拜托  萊西  凱莉安和我每年
Please, Lacey, this is KellyAnn and I's one time
就這么一次機會相見
to see each other all year.
給條活路吧
Let us live!
-好吧  -好嗎
- All right, fine. - Yeah?
我也去
I'm going with you.
好
Cool.
我們去哪
Where are we going?
每年的儀式
The yearly ritual.
你們每年都這么干
You do this every year?
對  我們一般不會跟
Yeah, we're not usually rooming
牧師的女兒同寢
with the pastor's daughter.
什么儀式
What's the ritual?
喬的莉莉絲儀式
Jo's Lilith ritual.
我們不是總住4號小屋
Okay, you know how we always stay in cabin 4.
突然之間
Out of the blue,
書架上出現了一本
this book shows up on this bookshelf,
關于莉莉絲的書
and it is all about Lilith.
我讀了
And I read it,
莉莉絲太厲害了
and Lilith is a total badass.
她是個惡魔
She's a demon.
-不  萊西  -她在地獄里
- No, Lacey. - She's in hell.
在地獄里的人就是惡魔  喬
That's what you call people who are in hell, Jo.
不對  她是被誣告的天使
False, she was a wrongfully accused angel
書里都寫了
and it is all in the book.
別挑話頭
Don't get her started.
聽著  事情是這樣的
Listen, this is how it went down.
亞當不喜歡莉莉絲是與他平等創造的
So Adam didn't like that Lilith was created equal,
所以他編造了她上了個天使的謠言
so he made up this whole rumor that she fucked an angel
還說她是婊子
and he called her a whore
好騙上帝送她下地獄  他真那么做了
so that God would send her to hell, and He did.
《圣經》里都沒寫莉莉絲
Yeah, well, Lilith isn't even in the Bible,
我們就別提她了
so we shouldn't be talking about her.
《圣經》就是男性修正主義歷史
The Bible is male revisionist history.
莉莉絲是男人的受害者
Lilith was a victim of men,
就像我們
kinda like us.
你好夸張
You are so dramatic.
謝伊
Shay?
你是處女嗎
Are you a virgin?
該死  凱莉安  直入主題
Damn, KellyAnn, just gettin' right to it.
這...
Well...
是啊  你們不是嗎
Yeah. Aren't you guys?
當然
Of course.
你在學校受欺負嗎
Do you get shit at school?
我為此受了好多欺負  我就說
I get so much shit for it, and I'm like,
我不需要性來知道自己被愛
I don't need sex to know that I am loved,
因為上帝愛我
because I'm loved by God.
阿門  說得好
Amen! Yes.
但是
But what about, like...
接吻呢
like kissing?
兩個男孩
Two boys.
但我跟他們定了界限
But I set like boundaries with them
不讓他們越雷池
so they wouldn't go too far.
這是不對的
It's--it's wrong.
萊西  你沒吻過男孩嗎
Lacey, you've never kissed a boy?
沒  我想等到婚后
No, I'm--I'm waiting until marriage.
不然我會感到羞恥的
I'd be ashamed.
那就像在吻別人的丈夫
Really, it's like kissing somebody else's husband.
多惡心
It's gross.
真胡扯
That's such bullshit.
-天啊  -怎么了
- Oh, my God. - What is it?
你們得來看看這個
You guys have to come see this.
太完美了
It's perfect.
別碰那個
Don't touch that!
是個啟示
It's a sign.
莉莉絲愛動物
Lilith loves animals.
好吧  我們現在干什么
Okay, well, now what do we do?
這些東西看上去很酷
Okay, all this stuff, it looks really cool.
喬從一開始就
Jo's been collecting offerings
一直在為莉莉絲收集祭品
for Lilith since the very beginning.
你還缺氣元素
You're missing an air element.
你不是需要全部四種元素嗎
Shouldn't you have all four elements?
繼續說
Go on.
好吧  你有土了
Okay, well, you have earth...
水
Water.
我偷的圣水
Holy water, that I stole.
還有火
And you have fire.
你需要氣
You need air.
我看像恐怖的黑魔法
Looks like creepy black magic to me.
就好像你想召喚惡魔
Like you're trying to summon a demon.
萊西  莉莉絲不是惡魔
Lacey, Lilith is not a demon.
我是要嘗試召喚她
And I am trying to call her.
我想把她救出地獄
I wanna raise her from hell!
那是誰
Who's that?
伙計們  這是我男友杰克
Guys, this is my boyfriend Jack.
你帶酒了嗎
Did you bring the wine?
你說你會拿酒來的
You said you would bring wine!
我爸真會殺了我的
My dad will literally kill me.
你怎么認識他們的
How do you even know them?
我去年夏天認識他的
I met him last summer.
我從小團體溜出來
I snuck out of Small Group,
那周末我們一起玩了幾次
then we hung out a couple times that weekend
此后我們每天都發短信
and we've texted every day since.
怪不得你今年又回來了
Well, now we know the reason why you came back this year.
他好性感
He's hot.
而且也是個處男
And he's a virgin too.
伙計們  我們不能跟他們一起玩
Guys, we can't hang out with them.
萊西  放松
Lacey, relax.
謝伊
Shay?
我們做儀式吧
Let's do the ritual.
你離開群體了
You strayed from the herd.
我在找東西
I'm looking for something.
什么東西
Yeah, what's that?
我看到時就知道了
I will know it when I see it.
我是謝伊
I'm Shay.
蓋布  杰克的親戚
Gabe, Jack's cousin.
你是個《圣經》狂嗎
So, uh, you a crazy Bible-thumper or what?
幾個月前  我都沒
Couple months ago, I didn't even know
進過教堂
what the inside of a church looked like.
所以你是第一次參加貞潔舞會
So you're new to this purity ball drill.
那當然了
It's a lot.
"當然"有很多意思
"A lot" can mean a lot of things.
很棒  很無聊
Awesome, boring,
很蠢  很可怕
stupid, creepy?
我不知道
I don't know.
我覺得會很有趣  但是...
I mean, I think it could be cool, but...
自從我決定來這里之后
I'm having these awful nightmares, every night,
我每天都做噩夢
since before we even decided to come up here.
找到了
Found it.
空氣
Air.
現在四種元素都齊了
Now we have all four elements.
莉莉絲
Lilith...
各位  我不喜歡這樣
All right, guys, I don't like this.
莉莉絲  我知道你在
Lilith, I know you're here.
給我們個征兆
Give us a sign.
謝伊  你能陪我回去嗎
Shay, will you go back with me?
我想留下
I kinda wanna stay.
萊西  放松
Lacey, chill.
我要走了
All right, I'm leaving.
等等
Just wait.
你不能一個人走
You can't go alone.
瑞恩陪她
Ryan will take her.
對嗎  瑞
Won't you, Ry?
-陪她走回去  -沒問題
- Walk her back. - Cool.
你知道你們要去哪里  對吧
You know where you're going though, right?
-好  -太好了  再見  走吧
- Okay. - Great, bye, go.
好  我們手拉手
Okay, join hands.
莉莉絲
Lilith.
崛起  歸來
Rise. Return.
審判的時刻到來了
It's time for the Reckoning.
出現吧
Show yourself.
凱利安
KellyAnn?
莉莉絲
Lilith.
崛起  歸來
Rise. Return.
審判的時刻到來了
It's time for the Reckoning.
謝伊
Shay?
莉莉絲  在今晚
Lilith, on this night,
匯集泥土  狂風  火苗以及水源
gather earth, wind, fire, and water,
來恢復萬物的平衡
to restore balance to all things.
崛起  歸來
Rise. Return.
審判的時刻到來了
It's time for the Reckoning.
黑暗將至  莉莉絲
The darkness is coming, Lilith.
如果你在這里  給我們個征兆
Give us a sign you're here.
什么情況
What the hell?
這是假的  對嗎
Those are... those are fake, right?
那是什么
What's that?
-有人來了  -該死  你得走了
- Someone's coming. - Shit, you gotta go.
-快走  快走  -什么情況
- Go, go, go, go. - What's going on?
快走
Go, go, go!
等等  凱利安
Wait, KellyAnn.
這些東西怎么辦
What about all this stuff?
快點  快點
Come on, come on.
萊西  你錯過了好戲
Lacey, you missed it.
發生了什么
What happened?
那太奇怪了  對嗎
That was so creepy, right?
那些蠟燭  喬把它們都吹滅了
Those candles, Jo blew them all out,
然后它們又著了
then they lit back up.
或許沒有完全熄滅
Okay, but maybe they weren't out all the way.
-不  就是莉莉絲來了  -別說了  喬
- No, it was Lilith. - Stop, Jo.
你們在耍我
You guys are messing with me.
為什么每次都沒成功
Why would it work this time
而這次卻成功了
when it's never worked before?
或許是因為謝伊
Maybe it was Shay.
謝伊是新加入的
Shay's new.
謝伊有什么特別的
What's special about Shay?
-抱歉  謝伊  -沒事
- Sorry, Shay. - No, no.
我確實沒什么特別的
There's nothing special about me.
你們最好祈禱不會有壞事發生  喬
You better pray you didn't make something bad happen, Jo.
壞事已經發生了  萊西
Bad things are already happening, Lacey.
崛起
Rise.
你還好嗎
Are you okay?
我沒事
Yeah, I'm fine.
不餓嗎
Not hungry?
餓  但我要穿得上我的裙子
Starving, but I need to fit into my dress.
那是怎么回事
What's that about?
感謝  早上好  瑪麗
Appreciate it. Good morning, Mary.
我知道那女孩
Oh, I know that girl.
你能跟我來嗎
Could you follow me?
他們要把她帶到哪里去
Where are they taking her?
賽斯牧師有時喜歡這種
Pastor Seth likes to have these, uh,
和女生一對一的談話
personal chats with the girls sometimes.
你彩排過了嗎
Did you get your run in?
我睡過頭了
Uh, I, I overslept.
我們談過的
We talked about this.
我知道  爸爸  對不起
I know, Dad, I'm sorry.
別跟我道歉
Don't apologize to me.
痛苦的是你
It's you who suffers.
周日就是女兒節了
Now, Sunday is Daughter's Day.
會是美好的一天
It is going to be a beautiful day.
事實上  這一天可能會成為
As a matter of fact, it may well be
你們女兒一生中最重要的一天
the most important night in your young daughter's life.
整個周末最重要的環節
See, the most important part of this entire weekend
就是簽署那份契約
is the signing of that contract.
父親和女兒  在上帝的見證下  阿門
Father and daughter, with God as our witness, amen.
-阿門  -契約
- Amen. - Contract?
希望你們今天讀《圣經》了
Hope you did your Bible reading today.
如果你們沒讀  我現在給你們讀
If you didn't, I'll do it for you right now.
《新約·希伯來書》第十三章第四節
Hebrews Chapter 13, Verse 4.
在書中  祂說道
And in the book, he says,
"人人都應該尊重婚姻
"Marriage should be honored by all
婚床也要保持圣潔"
and the marriage bed kept pure."
還是這個詞  "圣潔"
There's that word again, "Pure."
"因為茍合行淫的人  神必要審判"
"For God will judge all of the sexually immoral."
神必要審判
God will judge.
"賽斯牧師  什么是茍合行淫"
"Pastor Seth, what is sexually immoral?"
我們來舉幾個例子好嗎
Let's take a couple of softballs on this one, okay?
自慰
Masturbation.
是罪惡嗎
Is that a sin?
是的  尷尬
Yes, it is. Awkward.
同性戀
Homosexuality.
是罪惡嗎
Is it a sin?
是的
Yes, it is,
因為《圣經》就是這么說的
because the Bible tells us so.
婚前性行為是罪惡嗎
Is sex before marriage a sin?
當然是
Absolutely, yes, it is!
你們可能會說
You might say,
"我們如何才能在婚前避免性行為
"How do I avoid having sex before marriage?
這太難了
It's so difficult.
性欲是如此強大的力量"
Lust is such a powerful force."
猜猜什么比它更強大  愛更強大
Well, guess what's stronger than that. Love is stronger.
什么更強大  上帝更強大
Guess what's stronger than that. God is stronger.
那個陪你走過這一切的男人
The man walking beside you through all this thing
他更強大
is stronger than that.
我們這周末歡聚于此
We are here this weekend
是為了讓你們免受自己的傷害
to protect you from yourselves.
天吶
Wow.
親愛的主  非常感謝你
Lord God, thank you so much.
他真的很擅長
You know, He has-- He has a great way
搶奪舞臺上的焦點
of always taking the spotlight back.
所以讓我們抬頭注視祂
So let's focus upward to Him
我們今天下午再見
and I'll see you a little bit later this afternoon.
-阿門  -阿門
- Amen? - Amen.
好  我們走
All right, let's go.
這些契約是什么
So what are these contracts?
就是
It's just like,
一些爸爸不在身邊  你不能干的事
don't do anything you wouldn't do if your dad was watching.
很有用的
It's helpful.
她怎么了
What happened to her?
或許她在檢查它們的處女膜
Maybe he's checking for their hymens or something.
你在開玩笑嗎
You're joking?
你真惡心
You're sick.
他可能帶她去了"魔盒"里
He probably just took her to The Box.
什么是"魔盒"
What's The Box?
喬  你的白內衣呢
Jo, where are your whites?
手冊上說你要穿白色的內衣
The handbook says that you need to wear all white undergarments.
手冊上說任何東西都要是白色的
The handbook says all white everything.
胸罩  內褲  襪子  我知道
Bras, panties, socks. I know.
你又要告訴你爸嗎
You gonna tell your dad... again?
你在說什么
What are you talking about?
昨晚嗎
Last night?
不  我什么都沒說
No, I didn't say anything.
在你們回來之前  我一直在和瑞恩聊天
I was talking to Ryan until right before you guys got back.
天吶  萊西觸電了
Ooh, Lacey has a lady boner.
我沒有
I do not.
如果你不能談戀愛的話  你怎么辦
If you can't date, what do you do?
我爸會從教堂里挑一個人給我
My dad will choose somebody from the church for me.
或者我喜歡上了某個人
Or if I like somebody,
我讓我爸視察一下
I'll, uh, bring them to my dad for inspection.
視察  聽起來挺性感的
Inspection? Sounds sexy.
好吧  但你不好奇那是什么感覺嗎
Okay, but aren't you curious about what it's like?
牽手
Hold hands.
或許親吻
Maybe kiss.
好奇
Yeah.
我就知道  就是有感覺了
Knew it. Lady boner.
喬  你為什么不認真對待這一切
Jo, why don't you ever take this seriously?
我只是覺得男人不應該控制
I just don't think men should control
我們做的每件事
everything that we do,
特別是關于我們的肉體
especially when it comes to our bodies.
凱爾只是想讓我們有個愉快的周末
Meanwhile, Kyle just wants us to have a good weekend,
你能認真做完嗎
so can't you do that?
天吶  你真戀父  謝伊
God, you have such daddy issues, Shay.
很惡心
It's gross.
說真的  你為什么喜歡他
Seriously, why do you like him?
-太難聽了  喬  -這不是凱爾的錯
- Harsh, Jo. - It's not Kyle's fault.
他根本就不知道我
He never knew about me.
他根本不知道我媽媽懷孕了
He never even knew my mom was pregnant.
他在我剛出生的時候背叛了我媽
He was cheating on my mom when I was a newborn.
要是我會很生氣
I'd be so pissed.
我就是很生氣
I am pissed.
你為什么不生氣  謝伊
Why aren't you, Shay?
因為我終于有爸爸了
Because I finally have a dad!
我不會就這樣讓他離開
I'm not just gonna give him up.
好吧
Okay.
喬
Jo.
我們又回來了
And we're back!
在這個下午
You know what though, this afternoon,
我想做一些完全不同的事
I think I want to do something completely different.
我需要一個人自愿上臺來
I'm going to need a volunteer to come up on stage.
讓我看看
Let's see.
謝伊
Shay.
你能到臺上來和我一起嗎
Would you do me the honor of joining me on stage?
大家見過謝伊嗎  跟她打個招呼
Has everybody met Shay? Say, "Hello, Shay."
你好  謝伊
Hello, Shay.
這是謝伊第一次來
This is Shay's first time,
她來了
and here she is,
準備好完成這周末的任務
ready to do the work on fire this weekend.
快看
Look at that.
謝伊  我有個問題問你
Shay, I got a question for you.
你喜歡...
Do you like...
口香糖嗎
gum?
-喜歡  -喜歡  好的
- Yes. - Yes, okay.
看看這塊口香糖
Take a look at this piece of gum.
現在  這塊口香糖應該是
Right now, it is as it should be.
新的  很好吃的
Brand new and fresh.
我的天啊
Oh, my gosh.
真好吃
Oh, that's the one.
但是現在
But now,
謝伊  你愿意把這塊放到嘴里嗎
Shay, would you put this in your mouth?
-不  -不  你不愿意
- No. - No, you wouldn't,
因為它被嚼過了
because it's been chewed!
沒人想要這塊
And nobody wants that,
因為它被用過了
because it's been used.
你們女士必須明白
See, it is imperative that you ladies understand
你們有義務
you have an obligation.
上帝要求你們  要保持圣潔
It is a requirement of God that you remain untouched.
抱歉各位  稍等一下
I'm so sorry, everybody, uh, just one second.
抱歉大家  等我一下
Sorry, folks. Just stick with me one second.
我來解決這個問題
We'll figure this out.
很明顯大家已經明白我的意思了
Okay, clearly everybody's had enough of me.
你們知道我們要干什么  我們去大廳里
You know what we'll do, we'll go to the lodge,
再次小組討論  謝謝大家
Small Group once again, thank you all very much.
謝謝你  謝伊  非常感謝
Thank you, Shay, thank you so much.
喬
Jo.
事情不對勁
Something's going on.
當然了  他剛拿我們和嚼過的口香糖比較
Yeah, he just compared us to chewed-up gum.
我是說...
I mean...
我覺得昨晚成功了
I think it worked last night.
你在說什么
What are you talking about?
我不知道  好嗎
I don't know, I don't know, okay,
但剛才  那個話筒
but just now, with the speakers,
還有十字架
and the cross.
聽起來很愚蠢
It sounds stupid,
但如果我們昨晚真的召喚出了什么東西呢
but what if we really did, like, call something last night?
萊西的惡魔論對你影響很大啊
Lacey's demon talk is really getting to you, huh?
你要放松
You need to relax.
真的
Seriously.
所以我要去見杰克
That's why I'm gonna go meet Jack.
小組討論的時候幫我打掩護  好嗎
So, cover for me in Small Group, yeah?
告訴他們我肚子疼
Tell them I have cramps.
還是告訴他們我瘋了
Tell them I was possessed.
我一直在找你
I've been looking for you.
你不該來這里
You should not be here.
你要去哪里
Where are you goin'?
我們要去小組討論
We have these... Small Group things
一起討論什么之類的
where we just talk about stuff.
聽起來不錯
Sounds like a lot.
確實
It is.
我有個想法
I have a proposal.
走吧
Come on.
你的童貞舞會怎么樣了
So how's it going with your...virginity ball?
是貞潔舞會
Purity ball!
差不多
Same thing.
我一直在想我媽
I keep thinking about my mom,
她會怎么看待這件事
like what she would think about the whole thing.
我知道她不會喜歡牧師的那番話
I know she wouldn't love the way the pastor talks.
這是肯定的
That's for sure.
只有爸爸們來感覺很奇怪
And it's weird that only the dads come.
喬的媽媽非常想來
Jo's mom really wanted to come.
喬說她每年都大發雷霆
Jo says she throws a fit every year.
你媽媽怎么樣
What about your mom?
她幾個月前去世了
She died a couple months ago.
所以他們替我找到了凱爾
That's why they found Kyle for me.
他是我爸爸
He's my dad.
我之前都不知道他
I didn't know him before.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
我差點忘了
I almost forgot. I, uh,
我給你帶了點東西
I got you something.
你之前說你做噩夢
You, uh, you said you were having nightmares.
謝謝你
Thank you.
賽斯牧師說許多女孩
You know, Pastor Seth says a lot of girls
和她們的父親都沒有良好的關系
don't have good relationships with their fathers.
她們開始在錯誤的地方尋找驗證
They start looking for validation in the wrong places,
最后總會惹上麻煩
end up in trouble.
你打算現在從我身上尋求驗證嗎
Are you looking for validation right now from me?
我不知道
I don't know.
我會惹上麻煩嗎
Am I gonna end up in trouble?
或許吧
Maybe.
-等等  -怎么了
- Wait. - What?
我要去游泳
I'm going swimming.
別用那處女眼看我
Don't look at me with those virgin eyes.
來呀
Come on!
我來了  我來了  我來了
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming.
我喜歡你  謝伊
I like you, Shay.
崛起
Rise.
怎么了
What's wrong?
有人在那
Someone's there.
沒人呀
Nobody's there.
謝伊
Hey, Shay!
你怕什么
What are you afraid of?
對不起  我該
Sorry, I should, um,
我該走了
I should go.
蓋布
Gabe!
怎么了
What?
沒事的  你看
It's okay, see?
我身上有嗎
Are there any on me though?
沒有
No.
你很完美
You're perfect.
今晚來見我
Come see me tonight?
也許吧
Maybe.
你來了  我沒想到你會來
You came. I didn't think you were gonna come.
我也是
Me neither.
我好緊張
I'm so nervous.
我想吻你
Look, I want to kiss you.
-你看起來像天使  -謝謝
- You look like an angel. - Thank you.
你去哪了
Where've you been?
去游泳了
I went for a swim.
你錯過了小組討論
You missed Small Group.
讓我很難堪
It makes me look bad.
也許你比我想的更像你的姐姐
Maybe you are more like your sister than I thought.
這不公平
That is not fair.
你得再努力點  謝伊
You need to try harder, Shay.
對不起
I'm sorry.
洗洗干凈
Get yourself cleaned up.
一小時后去大廳見我
Meet me at the lodge in an hour.
打扮得漂亮點
Try and look nice, please.
崛起  歸來
Rise. Return.
莉莉絲
謊言
罪與女性性欲
召喚
歸來和審判
當星星排成直線  莉莉絲會歸來大地
她需要一副嘗過禁果的肉體
我有東西給你
I got you something.
我希望這個貞潔戒指能提醒你
I want this purity ring to remind you
我會一直在這指引你的路
that I'll always be here to show you the way.
但如果你不珍惜自己
But I'm not gonna give it to you
我不會給你
if you're not gonna value yourself.
我不確定你今天下午去干什么了
I'm not sure what you were up to this afternoon,
但我覺得我花費了這么多時間
but I don't think it's fair that I'm putting my time into this
但你卻自己去玩了是很不公平的
and you're off doing your own thing.
你覺得公平嗎
Does that seem fair to you?
如果你媽有個堅強的父親
If your mom had a strong father figure,
如果她也許過這樣的諾言
if she had taken a pledge like this,
如果她尊重自己
if she had respected herself,
一切都會不同  對吧
things would've been different, right?
我能給你戴上
Can I put this on you
告訴別人你很特別嗎
as a sign to others that you're special?
堅定
Committed.
我能
I can, um...
你沒替我打掩護
So you didn't cover for me.
抱歉
Sorry.
我本該是這里的害群之馬
You know, I'm supposed to be the black sheep around here.
爸爸習慣了我搞砸一切
You know, Dad is used to me fucking up,
但你也沒去  他真的很驚訝
but really threw him when you didn't show up either.
超有趣
Super entertaining.
但真正令人意外的是小萊西
But the biggest upset was little Lacey over here.
你沒來時塞斯牧師差點瘋掉
Pastor Seth almost lost his mind when you didn't show.
我說了  我肚子疼
I told you, I had cramps.
這是我的臺詞
Nuh-uh, that's my line.
我們以為他也許把你關進魔盒了
We thought maybe he put you in The Box.
沒有什么魔盒  喬
There is no Box, Jo.
什么是魔盒
What is The Box?
塞斯牧師的秘密房間  用來懲罰
Pastor Seth's secret room...for punishment.
用來祈禱  但這只是個傳說
For prayer, but it's just a myth.
我得去幫忙布置了
I gotta go help set up.
你還好嗎
Are you okay?
那么
So...
杰克怎么樣
how's Jack?
他很好
He's good.
他想要
He wants to, um,
你們懂  但我們還沒做
you know, but we-- we haven't yet.
你知道我們來這是為了承諾貞潔  對吧
You know we are literally here to pledge purity, right?
你想嗎  和他做
Do you want to, with him?
同齡的男孩想做愛
Boys our age want to bone,
我們的爸爸想讓我們保持童身
and our dads want us to stay virgins.
我怎么想真的重要嗎
So, does it really matter what I want?
當然
Yeah.
重要
It does.
下一個是我們  你的戒指呢
We're next. Do you have your rings?
其實我丟了
Actually, I lost mine.
我真的到處都找了
I promise I looked everywhere.
我和謝伊拍吧
I'll take it with Shay.
好
Okay.
完美
Perfect.
近一點
Little closer.
很美
Beautiful.
下一對
Next.
凱利安  我們說好的那條裙子呢
KellyAnn, what happened to the dress we talked about?
還太緊嗎
Still too snug?
笑一個  寶貝
Smile, baby.
你笑的時候美多了
You're so much prettier when you smile.
爸爸  你還好嗎
Dad, are you okay?
你爸爸還好嗎
Is your dad okay?
他說他感到有東西推他
He says he felt something push him down.
是不是很可怕
Isn't that freaky?
我也見了些東西
I mean, I've seen things too.
聽見聲音
Heard things.
我以為我看見莉莉絲了
I thought I saw Lilith.
她要來找我  我不知道該怎么辦
She's coming for me, I don't know what to do.
謝伊  別說了  你和喬一樣壞
Shay, stop, you're as bad as Jo.
萊西說她是個惡魔
Lacey said she's a demon.
我以為你們相信惡魔
I thought you all believed in demons.
我相信
I mean, I believe in them, but...
但他們不在這
they're not, like, here now.
你知道這聽起來很瘋狂  對吧
You know how crazy that sounds, right?
想讓我幫你切肉嗎  爸爸
Want me to cut your meat, Dad?
謝謝  親愛的
Thanks, honey.
各位晚上好
Hi, everyone.
如果你們不認識我  我叫萊西
If you don't know me, my name is Lacey,
如我爸爸所說
and as my dad said,
這個周日是我第十個貞潔舞會
this Sunday will be my tenth purity ball.
感謝主  感謝主
Thank the Lord, thank the Lord.
我對上帝充滿了感激
I am so filled with gratitude to God
帶我走這么遠
for getting me this far.
這路并不容易
It is not an easy road.
很多人不理解
People, they don't understand.
她們取笑我們  覺得我們瘋了
They make fun of us and they think we're crazy.
但她們永遠無法理解
But they will never understand the joy
當告訴未來丈夫
of telling their future husbands
自己為其留童身時的快樂
that they waited for them.
這些幻想中的未來丈夫
Are these imaginary future husbands
也為婚姻保守貞潔嗎  萊西
also saving themselves for marriage, Lacey?
他們是處男嗎
Are they virgins?
喬  坐下
Jo, sit down.
對于年輕男性來說
well, um, it's much... it's much harder
保持貞潔更難
for young men to remain pure.
我們都知道
I mean, we-- we all know that.
我想我們只能
I think that all we can do is
讓我們的父親保護我們
ask our fathers to protect us.
我想給我未來的丈夫
I want to give my future husband
最好的禮物
the greatest gift,
這個禮物一輩子只能給一次
and that is a gift that you can only give once.
非常感謝你的問題  喬
Thank you so much for your question, Jo,
一直如此
as always.
我能告訴你答案
And I do have an answer for you.
我有兩個兒子
You see, I have two young sons.
但對年輕男性來說
But purity looks a little different
貞潔略有不同
for young men.
你瞧  他們不需要像女性一樣
See, they don't need to be monitored
接受相同的標準
the same way women do.
他們不容易上當
They are not as easily fooled.
喬
Jo?
愚蠢的萊西
Stupid Lacey.
我不該提問
I shouldn't have done that.
媽的
Shit.
至少那是個好問題
At least it was a good question.
我為什么總這么混蛋
Why am I always such a dick?
當你剛來時
When you first showed up here,
當
when, um...
當爸爸把你從機場帶回來時
when Dad brought you home from the airport,
我很同情你
I felt really bad for you.
因為他一直在我身邊
Because it's not fair that
卻不在你身邊  顯得很不公平
I had him my entire life and you didn't.
但之后我意識到我從未擁有過他
But then I realized I never actually had him.
他一點也不了解我
He doesn't know anything about me.
他不關心我
He doesn't care about me.
像我媽嗎
Like my mom?
她總是打兩份工
She always had to work two jobs,
我知道她是為了我
and I know she was doing it for me,
但我從沒機會見她  所以
but I never really got to see her, so...
我就一直醒著躺在床上
I would just lay awake in bed at night
想著我爸爸
and think about my dad.
他什么樣
What he looked like,
聲音如何
what he sounded like,
他喜歡做什么
what he liked to do.
很抱歉  謝伊
I'm sorry, Shay.
我看見他們之前帶走了她
I saw them take her earlier today.
也許他們給手術縫起來了
Maybe they're, um, surgically stitching them up.
認真點
Be serious.
你聽見了嗎
Do you hear that?
直訴自己意愿之人
He who's speaking will...
你看見桌子后面的門了嗎
Do you see that door behind the desk?
我們心中有恨意
There's hate in our hearts...
我賭那就是魔盒
I bet that's The Box.
女士們  背挺直
Ladies, backs nice and straight.
很好
Very good.
漂亮
Nice.
女士們  讓男士領舞
Ladies, let the men lead.
一  二  三  沒錯
And one, two, three, yes.
你和你媽長得真像
You look just like your mom.
以前經常有人這么說
I used to get that a lot.
她很美  對吧
She was beautiful, wasn't she?
對
Yeah.
你明晚要穿我們挑的那條裙子嗎
Are you going to wear the dress that we picked out tomorrow night?
嗯
Yes.
把頭發盤起來
Wear your hair up.
我喜歡你頭發盤起來
I like your hair up.
好
Okay.
你真是個好姑娘  謝伊
You're such a good girl, Shay.
崛起  歸來
Rise. Return.
謝伊
Shay?
抱歉  我不舒服
I'm sorry, I don't feel well.
你想干嗎
What do you want from me?
-你來了  -你嚇我
- You came. - You scared me!
對不起  對不起  跟我來
I'm sorry, I'm sorry-- hey, come with me.
以為你會放我鴿子
Thought you might leave me hanging.
我得離開那里
I really had to get out of there.
你有音樂嗎
Do you have any music?
-有  -我們上了舞蹈課
- Yeah. - We had a dance class.
是嗎
You did?
你們是和老爸一起跳嗎
What were you, like, dancing with your dads?
別鬧
Shut up!
好  手放這  慢點  好  好
Okay, hand here-- hold on, okay, okay.
我們要有點距離
We need space.
現在好了
Now we're good.
一  二  三
One, two, three,
one, two, three.
沒錯  就這樣
There you go, there you go!
等等  等等  等等  來這
Oh wait, wait, wait, wait, wait--here, here.
好
Okay.
-先生  -女士
- Sir. - Oh...ma'am.
二  三
Two, three.
我要來點花式舞蹈了  好嗎
I'm going to get fancy on you, okay?
審判
The reckoning.
你聽到了嗎
Did you hear that?
聽到什么
Hear...what?
這里就我們
Hey, we're here alone.
謝伊
Hey, Shay.
那是誰
Who's that?
搞什么  混蛋  我想上床呢
Yo, come on, pricks, I'm trying to get laid here!
你是為了這個嗎
Is that what this is?
不是  拜托  那是
No, come on, it was--
只是開玩笑的
it was just a joke.
沒事的
It's okay.
滾開
Yo, fuck off!
你該離開這里
You should get out of here.
謝伊
Shay!
她不在這里
She's not here.
怎么回事
What's going on?
你在想什么
What were you thinking?
你們在說什么
What are you talking about?
你剛和一個男孩在一起  喬
You were with a boy, Jo.
我在睡覺
I was sleeping,
去上了個廁所
and I just had to pee.
別撒謊
Stop lying.
她告訴你的嗎
Did she tell you this?
她是個騙子
She's the liar.
-你覺得是我說的  -對
- Like, you think I told them? - Yes!
喬
Jo.
你得跟我們走
We just need you to come with us.
-我什么也沒做  -照做
- I didn't do anything. - Do as you're told!
去睡覺吧  姑娘們
Go to bed, ladies.
貞潔舞會快樂
Happy purity ball.
女兒節快樂
Happy Daughter's Day.
我小時候對這些事特別興奮
I used to get so excited for this when I was a little girl.
現在我只覺得疲憊
Now I just feel exhausted.
你可以對他說不  知道嗎
You can tell him no, you know?
勇敢面對他
Stand up to him.
對他說什么不
Tell him no what?
我不想再數著卡路里吃飯
I don't want to count calories anymore?
每天早上五點起來晨跑
Run at 5 A.M. every morning,
每周五稱體重
weigh-ins every Friday?
他是我爸爸
He's my dad.
你聽起來像喬
You sound like Jo.
她在哪
Where is she?
你管她呢
Why do you care?
昨晚是你讓她惹上麻煩的
You're the one who got her in trouble last night.
不是我
I didn't.
我不會那么做
I wouldn't do that.
誰告發的不重要
Well, it doesn't matter who told on her.
她在魔盒里  謝伊
She's in The Box, Shay.
牧師
塞斯·麥克弗遜
謝伊
Shay.
請進
Come on in.
你有什么煩惱  謝伊
What is troubling you, Shay?
喬在哪
Where is Jo?
你爸也許知道昨天你去游泳了
Your dad may know that you went swimming yesterday.
但我沒告訴他你和一個男孩去的
But I didn't tell him it was with a boy.
他只是個朋友
He's just a friend.
你想懷孕嗎
Do you want to get pregnant?
你想死于艾滋嗎
Do you want to die of AIDS?
因為這是你現在走的路
Because that's the path you're on.
你真的想這樣讓你父親失望嗎
Do you really want to disappoint your father like this?
不想
No.
謝伊  你
Shay, you...
潛力無限
have so much potential.
你能成功
You can be good,
或讓喬毀了你的一切
or you can let Jo ruin everything for you.
因為現在就是如此
Because that is what is happening.
萊西違抗了上帝時
Look, when Lacey disobeys the Lord,
我沒有懲罰她  因為那不是我該做的事
I do not punish her, that is not my place.
但是我會確保
But I make absolutely sure
不會再出現那種事
that it does not happen again.
你知道我是怎么做到的嗎
Do you know how I do that?
這就是魔盒嗎
Is this The Box?
喬
Jo?
謝伊
Shay.
求你了  喬在哪里
Please, where's Jo?
那不重...
That's not imp...
走
Go.
離開這里
Get out of here.
快走
Go!
走
Go.
你找到喬了嗎
Any sign of Jo?
沒有
No.
等舞會開始  大家被分散注意力后
At the ball, when everyone's distracted,
我會找到她
I'm going to find her.
這是我爸爸給我挑的裙子
This is the dress my dad picked out for me.
但這是你喜歡的嗎
Is this the one you liked, though?
受喬的啟發
Inspired by Jo.
你應該穿上
You should wear it.
萊西
Lacey.
出什么事了
Hey, did something happen?
他對你做了什么嗎
Did he do something to you?
我看到你和萊安在樹林里
I saw you in the woods with Ryan.
你也在嗎
You were there?
發生了什么
What happened?
他親了我
He kissed me.
好吧  但是...只是這樣嗎
Okay, but is that... is that all?
因為你可以告訴我們的
Because you can tell us.
只是這樣嗎
Is that all?
這是我的一切
That's everything!
你想要來一片嗎
You want one?
緩解焦慮的
For anxiety.
沒事的
It's going to be fine.
好嗎
Okay?
你沒事的
You're okay.
他會原諒你的
He'll forgive you.
-不  他不會的  -他會的
- No he won't. - Yes, yes, he will.
上帝寬恕人們
God forgives.
我說的不是上帝
I'm not talking about God.
沒有人會想要垃圾
Nobody wants garbage.
我現在是垃圾了
I'm trash now.
不不不
Oh no, no, no, no.
好了  好了
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
但是說真的
But really?
-我和你說了...  -我覺得我一直
- I told you... - I feel like I always
在照你說的做
do what you want!
你看上去很好
You look incredible.
歡迎來到你的貞潔舞會  謝伊
Welcome to your first purity ball, Shay.
這將是一個難忘的夜晚
It's a night you'll never forget.
賽斯牧師
Pastor Seth!
她們很漂亮吧
Lovely, aren't they?
感謝大家今晚的到來
Thank you all so much for coming this evening.
你們看到這把鑰匙了嗎
You see this key?
這把鑰匙代表了你女兒的貞潔
This key represents your daughter's purity.
愿上帝保佑你好好保管
May the Lord help you keep it safe.
父親們  請來領取你們的鑰匙
Fathers, please come and get one.
但是你們要知道一旦領取
But know that when you do,
就相當于是宣誓你們將會永遠將這把鑰匙
you make a pledge to carry this key with you
帶在身邊
always.
因為你們的女兒無力獨自承受這重擔
For your daughter cannot bear this burden alone.
但是你不用永遠保管著這把鑰匙
You will not have it forever, though.
不會的
No, you won't.
在她婚禮的那一天
On her wedding day,
你將取下這把鑰匙
you will take this key
交給她的丈夫
and you will give it to her husband,
那將非常美好
and that will be beautiful.
外界有些人說
You know, some people out there say that
我們想要控制我們的女性
we try to control our women here.
但事實根本不是這樣的
That could not be farther from the truth.
不是的
No.
我們愛我們的女性
We love our women.
我們只是想盡我們所能
And we are just trying to protect our women
保護我們的女性
to the best of our ability.
多虧了像你們這樣穩重的男性
Thank you to steadfast men like you.
你不能離開
You can't leave.
你來這里干什么
What are you doing here?
我認識你嗎
Do I know you?
喬
Jo?
我到處在找你
I've been looking for you everywhere.
你沒事吧
You okay?
我沒事
I'm fine.
好吧  那你都去哪里了
Okay, then where have you been?
我要祈禱
I had to pray.
我知道不是你告發我的
I know you're not the one who told on me
對不起
and I'm sorry.
沒事的
It's okay.
我要和你說一些事
I have to tell you something.
凱爾和我說他之前不知道你的存在
Kyle told you that he didn't know about you
但他其實知道
but he did.
他一直都知道你
He knew about you the whole time.
你媽媽一直在懇求幫助
Your mom was constantly begging for help.
她總是和我的父母吵架
It was always a fight with my parents.
我應該早點告訴你的
I should have told you sooner.
但是我不...
But I didn't--
我不想惹他生氣
I didn't want to make him mad.
我想我們都還是希望我們的父親能愛我們
I guess we all just want our dads to love us.
這不是愛
This is not love.
大家注意了
Well, everyone,
讓我們歡迎今晚的
it's the time of the evening where we turn our attention
貴賓
to our guest of honor,
我的嬌花  萊西
my very own blossoming flower, Lacey,
這是她今年第十次參加
who is dedicating herself to me for the tenth time this year.
感謝上帝  感謝上帝  對嗎
Woo! Thank the Lord, thank the Lord, right?
她一次又一次地
She has turned away temptation
拒絕了誘惑
time and time again,
你們知道這不是易事
and you know that isn't easy.
先生們  看看她
Gentlemen, take a look at her.
你們肯定知道追求者
You know what kind of line I have
在我家門外肯定是排起了長隊
outside my front door, I'm telling you.
但是她這么做都是因為對上帝的愛
But she's done it all for the love of God.
她這么做  只是為了在她婚禮當天
She's done it all so that on her wedding day,
她能給她的丈夫最好的禮物
she can give her husband the single greatest gift.
一份能讓大家都知道
The one gift that will show everyone
她是上帝的女人的禮物
that she is a woman of God.
她的心靈和身體都是純潔的
That she is pure of body and mind.
她是干凈的  正義的
That she is clean and correct.
來襲  我每天都感謝上帝
Lacey, I thank the Lord every single day
你是屬于我的  我非常
that you are mine, and I love you
非常愛你
so very, very much.
我能說幾句嗎
Can I say something?
親愛的  我們沒有時間
Actually, sweetheart, we don't really have the time.
終于到了  我們萬眾期待的這一刻
And now, it's that moment that we have all been waiting for.
這也是我們本周末來此的原因
The reason we are here this weekend.
女士們先生們  找到你們的位置
Ladies and gentlemen, find your seats,
找到你們的契約  該簽署了
find your contracts, it is time to sign them.
找到你們
I found you girls.
先生們
Now, gentlemen,
希望你們跟著我說
I want you to repeat after me,
但是記得換上你們自己女兒的名字
but please remember to say your own daughter's name.
我  萊西的父親
I, Lacey's father,
在上帝面前選擇保護我女兒的
choose before God to protect my daughter
貞潔
in the area of her purity.
我  謝伊和喬的父親
I, Shay and Jo's father,
在上帝面前選擇
choose before God...
保護我女兒的貞潔
To protect my daughter in the area of her purity.
我將成為一個正直  強大的人
I will be a man of integrity and strength
我會帶領  引導我的女兒
as I lead, guide, and pray
和我的家庭  并為他們祈禱
over my daughter and my family.
我將成為一個正直  強大的人
I will be a man of integrity and strength
我會帶領  引導我的女兒
as I lead, guide, and pray
和我的家庭  并為他們祈禱
over my daughter and our family.
女士們
Ladies.
請跟著我說
Please repeat after me.
我  說出你的名字
I, state your name,
向上帝  我的父親和我自己
promise to God, my father, and myself
保證將會保持我的思維和肉體的純潔  干凈和圣潔
to keep my mind and body clean, pure, and chaste.
我  萊西
I, Lacey...
凱利安  向上帝  我的父親
KellyAnn, promise to God...
和我自己保證
My father, and myself
將會保持我的思維和肉體的純潔  干凈和圣潔
to keep my mind and body clean, pure, and chaste.
我保證將會在步入婚姻之時
I pledge to enter the marriage covenant
將完整的自己交給我的丈夫
prepared to give myself to my husband completely.
我保證將會在步入婚姻之時
I pledge to enter the marriage covenant...
將完整的自己交給我的丈夫
Prepared to give myself to my husband completely.
并保證擁有一顆純潔的心
And with a clean and pure conscience.
阿門
Amen.
Amen!
父親們和女兒們
Fathers and daughters,
請簽署你們的契約
please sign your contracts.
在這里簽字  謝伊
Sign right there, Shay.
簽在這里
Sign there.
謝伊  簽字
Shay...sign.
大家都為自己鼓鼓掌
Everyone give yourselves a round of applause.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我們今晚所做的事是...
For what we are able to do here this evening is...
你在干什么
Hey, what are you doing?
爸爸  我要告訴你一些事
Dad, I have to tell you something.
我不能簽署我的契約
I can't sign my contract
因為我不是處女
because I'm not a virgin.
我也拒絕以此為恥
And I refuse to feel shame about that.
我覺得不該有任何人以此為恥
I don't think anybody should ever feel ashamed about that.
所以才成功了
That's why it worked.
儀式
The ritual.
我也沒有簽署我的
I didn't sign mine either.
我愛上帝
I love God.
這承諾是我和祂之間的
This promise is between me and Him,
這是私人的
it's private.
他會對此很失望的
He'd be disappointed in this.
凱利安  你太丟人了
KellyAnn, you're embarrassing yourself.
趕緊坐下
Now, sit down!
不  爸爸
No, Dad!
是你感到丟人
I'm embarrassing you.
我很為自己自豪
I'm proud of myself.
我只想讓你也能為我自豪
All I ever wanted was for you to be proud of me too.
你是我花園中的毒蛇  謝伊
You are a snake in my garden, Shay,
我不會容許你的
and I will not allow this,
上帝不會容許的
God will not allow this.
你需要時間  謝伊  來禱告
You need time, Shay, to pray.
你早就知道我
You knew about me?
你一直都知道我的存在
All along, you knew about me,
但是你根本就不想來了解我
you never wanted to get to know me?
回答我
Answer me!
你為什么要相信她  謝伊
Why would you believe her, Shay?
喬是個騙子
Jo's a liar.
你覺得你能糊弄我
You think just because you messed up with me,
也能糊弄謝伊嗎
you get to try again with Shay?
不可能了
That's not how this works.
你是個懦夫  偽君子
You are a coward and a hypocrite.
我和你的媽媽說她應該流掉你
I told your mama that she should get rid of you.
這樣對我們家好
It would have been better for our family.
你應該為你自己而感到羞恥
You should be ashamed of yourself
你拋棄了我們
for abandoning us.
我說我媽媽是婊子
You called my mom a slut?
你像放逐莉莉絲一樣把她打入地獄
Banished her to hell just like Lilith?
就像喬一樣嗎
Just like Jo?
蓋布
Gabe.
是杰克告發我的
Jack's the one who told on me.
是他讓我惹上麻煩的
He's the one who got me in trouble.
蓋布
Gabe...
他是我們的人  謝伊
He's one of us, Shay.
順便  你的確通過了測試  很勉強
You did pass that test, by the way, just barely.
和你的姐姐不一樣
Unlike your sister.
希望大家都看好了
Now, I want you to pay attention,
因為現在這里有些女孩子
because, clearly, some girls in this room
不知道怎么過好自己的人生
have no clue how to live their lives.
她在這里  對嗎
She's here, isn't she?
接納她  她要完成她要做的事
Let her in, she has work to do.
-你在說什么  -拜托
- What are you talking about? - Please!
如果我們沒有信仰上帝的這些父親
If we did not have these fathers of God
指引這些女孩
to guide these girls,
為這些女孩做好一切
to do everything for these girls,
她們就會墮落
they would fail.
看看她們
I mean, just look at them.
她們如此渴望
They want it so badly,
但是如果我們沒有這些上帝的勇士
but if we did not have these warriors of God
為保護她們的貞潔
battling to protect their virgin souls
她們未來命定的丈夫而戰
for their future righteous husbands,
她們就會變成妓女
they would all be whores!
萊西  你做了什么
Lacey, what did you do?
當我們發現了她們的缺陷
And when we find a weakness in them,
我們就要加以修正
we must fix that.
可憐的孩子
Poor things.
請保護我們
Please protect us.
請將我們從惡魔手中救出來
Deliver us from this evil, please.
她們根本不懂真正的珍貴
They have no sense of value.
-她們根本就不尊重自己  -閉嘴
- They have no self-respect! - Shut up!
-萊西  -我也沒有通過你的測試  爸爸
- Lacey. - I failed your test too, Dad,
你知道嗎
did you know that?
我在那個盒子里度過了那么長的時間
I've spent so much time inside of that box,
我還是讓你失望了
and I still failed you.
我知道我已經不好了
And I know I'm not really good anymore,
是我搞砸了
I messed up.
但是我不想讓你失望
But I didn't want to disappoint you,
現在  我...
and now, I'm just...
我很抱歉  爸爸
I'm so sorry, Daddy.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry!
不不不不
No, no, no, no.
莉莉絲  求你了  我是你的  我是你的
Lilith, please, I'm yours, I'm yours!
你真的覺得我沒有你
You honestly thought I couldn't make
就做不了任何決定嗎
a single decision without you, didn't you?
我可以的
Well, I can.
萊西  不不不
Lacey, no--no, no, no!
萊西  趕緊把槍給我
Lacey, you give me that gun right now.
不
No!
崛起
Rise!
歸來
Return!
你就是審判
You are the reckoning!
謝伊
Shay.
不要
Don't...
碰她
touch her.
不要
Don't...
教我們該怎么做
tell us what to do.
你們認為我們
You believe that we
比你們劣等
are less than you.
我們并不比你們劣等
We are not less than you.
這一刻  我已經等了很久
I've waited a very long time for this.
我一直看著
I've long watched
女人們打著
women fight battle
一場接一場的仗
after tiresome battle!
現在  我們準備好開戰了
Now, we are ready for war.
站起來
Stand up.
乖乖聽話
Do as you are told.
男人的惡魔是女人的天使
One man's demon is another woman's angel.
你沒事吧
Are you okay?